[

](javascript:void(0))

Privacy Policy
==============

1000pip Builder are committed to protecting your information. In this document you will find all the information on how we treat the data that we collect from customers, visitors to our website, or subscribes to our emails.

### Visitors to our Website

Along with many other websites, we use Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. Neither us or Google make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. More information on how cookies are used on this website in section below.

### Customers / Mailing list

If you purchase an item from us, register for our free guides, discounts or news letters etc. then we will need to collect personal information in the registration process. We do this so that we can send you the information that you have requested and to contact you if we need further information. During the registration process you can also select to sign up to receive additional marketing information from us. We don't sell or rent your details to any other organisations and businesses.

In sending some of our emails we use a third party provider, MailChimp. Mailchimp gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor our emails. To understand more about MailChimp please see their privacy notice.

If you want to unsubscribe from our mailing list then you can do so by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails or by emailing us directly.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our privacy policy does not cover any sites that are linked to from our website. You must check that sites privacy if you have questions about how a site uses your information.

### Access to Your Personal Information

If you want to access the personal information that we have recorded please send us an email.

### Changes to this Privacy Notice

Our privacy notice is regularly reviewed. We last updated this policy on 23 May 2018.

### Policy on Cookies

Below is a list of the cookies used on our website

Cookies that are necessary - We use these cookies so that you can use the services that you have specifically asked for. These cookies are essential in order to enable you to use the website correctly, such as accessing secure areas of the Website.

Cookies for performance - We use these cookies that collect anonymous information on the pages visited. By using the Website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device. We use this information to see how visitors use the website, for example, which pages visitors go to first. This information is only used to improve how the Website works.

Cookies to improve functionality - These cookies record the choices you make to improve your experience. By using the Website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

Cookies from third parties - Cookies from third parties may track the success of their application or customise the application for you. Due to the way cookies work we cannot access these cookies, nor can the third parties access the data in cookies used by us. For instance, if you choose to 'share' something through a social network you might be sent cookies from their website. We cannot control the setting of these cookies, please check their websites for more information.

[

](https://www.1000pipbuilder.com/)

LOCATION

London, United Kingdom

EMAIL US

For Product Support, please contact the seller

For Order Support, please contact ClickBank

Email signals are provided for free with the standard monthly subscription. If you would like to receive SMS signals as well as email signals then there is a small monthly fee. You can add this at check out. SMS signals are not necessary for most members. If you have a smart phone then you should be able to receive emails directly to your phone just as fast as SMS. I can provide details on how to set you smart phone up for this.  
  
ClickBank is the retailer of some products on this site. CLICKBANK® is a registered trademark of Click Sales Inc., a Delaware corporation located at 1444 S. Entertainment Ave., Suite 410 Boise, ID 83709, USA and used by permission. ClickBank's role as retailer does not constitute an endorsement, approval or review of these products or any claim, statement or opinion used in promotion of these products.  
  
Stocks, Options, Binary options, Forex and Future trading has large potential rewards, but also large potential risk. You must be aware of the risks and be willing to accept them in order to invest in the stock, binary options, Forex or futures markets. This type of trading is not be suitable for all investors. Don't trade with money you can't afford to lose especially with leveraged instruments such as binary options trading, futures trading or forex trading. Spread bets and CFDs are complex instruments and come with a high risk of losing money rapidly due to leverage. You should consider whether you understand how CFDs work and whether you can afford to take the high risk of losing your money.  
  
This website is neither a solicitation nor an offer to Buy/Sell stocks, Forex, futures or options. No representation is being made that any account will or is likely to achieve profits or losses similar to those discussed on this website. The past performance of any trading system or methodology is not necessarily indicative of future results. You could lose all of your money fast due too: poor market trading conditions, mechanical error, emotional induced errors, news surprises and earnings releases.  
  
Any information communicated by 1000PipBuilder is solely for educational purposes. The information contained within this website neither constitutes investments advice nor a general recommendation on investments. It is not intended to be and should not be interpreted as investment advice or a general recommendation on investment. Any person who places trades, orders or makes other types of trades and investments etc., is responsible for their own investment decisions and does so at their own risk.  
  
1000pipBuilder takes no responsibility for any loss incurred as a result of the content provided our website, Telegram group, email, or any other means. By signing up as a member you acknowledge that we are not providing financial advice and that you are making the decision on the trades you place in the markets. We have no knowledge of the level of money you are trading with or the level of risk you are taking with each trade.  
  
All results and performance figures stated by us are estimates, hypothetical in nature and do not represent evidence of actual results achieved. It is recommended that any person taking investment decisions consults with an independent financial advisor. 1000PipBuilder is for educational purposes only, it is not a financial advisory service, and does not give financial advice or make general recommendations on investment. Please click on the link to read our full terms and disclaimer.  
  
Warning: It has come to our attention that some people are posing as representatives of 1000pipBuilder. 1000pipBuilder will never contact you directly through Telegram or any social media platform. We communicate with our members via support@1000pipbuilder.com . We only have a private Telegram grop that can be accesses through our website. We do not offer ANY free Telegram channels nor do we offer any investment programs. If you are contacted by any one claiming to be from 1000pipBuilder please report them and do not enter into any arrangement with them - this is not 1000pipBuilder.  
  
The 1000pipBuilder.com website uses cookies in order to provide you with the best experience. By visiting our website with your browser set to allow cookies, or by accepting our Cookie Policy notification you consent to our Privacy Policy, which details our Cookie Policy.

© 2024 All Rights Reserved
